{
    "id": "bc45133d528e441d905a5846eb176051",
    "title": "Idioms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "A cock and bull story is ……………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a foolish, unbelievable story",
                "a dead letter",
                "an epic"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Training is …………………… .. to a doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "inseparable",
                "indispensable",
                "irrefutable"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is a website for students …………………… . mother language is not English.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "whose",
                "of whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When I asked them who took the money, the boys ……………………… ignorance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "affected",
                "effected",
                "acted"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A good manager should …………………… . from criticizing his subordinates.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "abstain",
                "refrain",
                "avoid"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was an ………………… in the murder.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "accomplice",
                "accessary",
                "accessory"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "When people ………………… . ill, they consult their doctor hoping to get the best medical care.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "turn",
                "go",
                "fall"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This is Mrs. Seth …………………… . they say is the best pianist in the town.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is high time she ………………… . the dues.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pay",
                "pays",
                "paid",
                "has paid"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He tiptoed into the room lest he …………………. the baby.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wake up",
                "should wake up",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}